{
    "qns1":{
        "question": "Who is Mickey Mouse’s girlfriend?",
        "correct_answer": "Minnie",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Pluto",
            "Goofy",
            "Donald Duck"
        ]
    },
    "qns2":{
        "question": "What kind of animal is Pororo?",
        "correct_answer": "Penguin",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Crocodile",
            "Polar Bear",
            "Fox"
        ]
    },
    "qns3":{
        "question": "There’s a starfish called Patrick and a snail called Gary. Which show is it?",
        "correct_answer": "SpongeBob SquarePants",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "The Super Mario Bros. Super Show!",
            "Phineas and Ferb",
            "Adventure Time"
        ]
    },
    "qns4":{
        "question": "I am yellow and square. My best friend is a star shaped pink guy. We both live under the sea. Which cartoon character am I?",
        "correct_answer": "SpongeBob SquarePants",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Patrick",
            "Sandy",
            "Gary"
        ]
    },
    "qns5":{
        "question": "I am part of a team of super sleuths who solve mysteries and chase monsters. Even though I am a dog, I can still speak, though not clearly. Who am I?",
        "correct_answer": "Scooby-Doo",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Velma Dinkley",
            "Fred Jones",
            "Shaggy Rogers"
        ]
    },
    "qns6":{
        "question": "Where do SpongeBob SquarePants and his friends live?",
        "correct_answer": "Bikini bottom",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Under the sea",
            "Rock house",
            "Pineapple house"
        ]
    },
    "qns7":{
        "question": "I am coloured gray and love toying with bald hunters. What is my name?",
        "correct_answer": "Bugs Bunny",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Daffy Duck",
            "Elmer Fudd",
            "Tweety"
        ]
    },
    "qns8":{
        "question": "What TV show contains a purple dinosaur who sings and dances?",
        "correct_answer": "Barney and Friends",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Paw Patrol",
            "Hello Kitty and Friends Supercute Adventures",
            "Peppa Pig"
        ]
    },
    "qns9":{
        "question": "While Sandy was hibernating, what kind of weather did SpongeBob and Patrick encounter in the bubble where she lives?",
        "correct_answer": "Snow",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Hurricane",
            "Extreme heat",
            "Tornado"
        ]
    },
    "qns10":{
        "question": "What are the colors of the Powerpuff girls?",
        "correct_answer": "All of the above",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Red",
            "Blue",
            "Green"
        ]
    },
    "qns11":{
        "question": "What are the names of Powerpuff girls?",
        "correct_answer": "All of the above",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Blossom",
            "Bubbles",
            "Buttercup"
        ]
    },
    "qns12":{
        "question": "My brother, Ferb, and I like to invent things to enjoy the long summer days. We've made a rollercoaster, a new season and even a haunted house. We annoy my sister, Candace, a lot with our antics. Who am I?",
        "correct_answer": "Phineas Flynn",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Perry the Platypus",
            "Dr. Heinz Doofenshmirtz",
            "Jeremy Johnson"
        ]
    },
    "qns13":{
        "question": "What are the names of the bears in We Bare Bears?",
        "correct_answer": "All of the above",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Grizzly",
            "Panda",
            "Ice Bear"
        ]
    },
    "qns14":{
        "question": "Name the type of bears in We Bare Bears?",
        "correct_answer": "All of the above",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Panda",
            "Polar Bear",
            "Brown Bear"
        ]
    },
    "qns15":{
        "question": "Who taught Ice Bear to cook in We Bare Bears?",
        "correct_answer": "Yuri",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Chloe",
            "Yana",
            "Nom Nom"
        ]
    },
    "qns16":{
        "question": "What is the color of Dorami, Doraemon's sister?",
        "correct_answer": "Yellow",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Pink",
            "Orange",
            "Purple"
        ]
    },
    "qns17":{
        "question": "Who is Elsa’s sister in Frozen?",
        "correct_answer": "Anna",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Cassandra",
            "Elspeth",
            "Sharon"
        ]
    },
    "qns18":{
        "question": "What does Elsa wear to help protect others from her powers?",
        "correct_answer": "Gloves",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "A beanie",
            "Sunglasses",
            "A scarf"
        ]
    },
    "qns19":{
        "question": "What is the name of the snowman Elsa brought to life?",
        "correct_answer": "Olaf",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Kristian",
            "Oaken",
            "Hans"
        ]
    },
    "qns20":{
        "question": "Is Elsa older than her sister?",
        "correct_answer": "Yes",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "No",
            "I don't know",
            "Maybe"
        ]
    },
    "qns21":{
        "question": "What does she make while singing Let It Go?",
        "correct_answer": "Her Ice Castle",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "A cake",
            "A cup of tea",
            "A new dress"
        ]
    },
    "qns22":{
        "question": "Who is the captian of the teamin Paw Patrol?",
        "correct_answer": "Ryder",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Skye",
            "Tracker",
            "Rubble"
        ]
    },
    "qns23":{
        "question": "How many pups are there in the whole team?",
        "correct_answer": "8",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "4",
            "5",
            "6"
        ]
    },
    "qns24":{
        "question": "Who is Everest?",
        "correct_answer": "Snow Pup",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Construction Pup",
            "Sea Pup",
            "Jungle Pup"
        ]
    },
    "qns25":{
        "question": "Who is Skye?",
        "correct_answer": "Air Pup",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Sea Pup",
            "Police Pup",
            "Recycle Pup"
        ]
    },
    "qns26":{
        "question": "Who is the mayor of Adventure Bay?",
        "correct_answer": "Mayor Goodway",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Chikaleka",
            "Mayor Humdinger",
            "Ryder"
        ]
    },
    "qns27":{
        "question": "How many kittens does Mayor Humdinger have?",
        "correct_answer": "6",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "4",
            "5",
            "8"
        ]
    },
    "qns28":{
        "question": "What is the favorite show of Paw Patrol?",
        "correct_answer": "Apollo the Super-Pup",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Tag-war",
            "Pup pup Boogie",
            "Hit the Target "
        ]
    },
    "qns29":{
        "question": "What is the name of Hello Kitty's twin sister?",
        "correct_answer": "Mimmy",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Millie",
            "Julie",
            "Lily"
        ]
    },
    "qns30":{
        "question": "Where does Hello Kitty live?",
        "correct_answer": "London, England",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "New York City",
            "Japan",
            "Paris"
        ]
    },
    "qns31":{
        "question": "",
        "correct_answer": "",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ]
    },
}